[
    {
        "Question": "mutually beneficial",
        "Answer": "helpful to one another",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mutually exclusive",
        "Answer": "if one of the theories is true, then all the others must be false",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "myriad",
        "Answer": "many",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "neglected",
        "Answer": "failed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "negligible",
        "Answer": "minor",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "nonetheless",
        "Answer": "however",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "norms",
        "Answer": "rules",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "notably",
        "Answer": "particularly",
        "Options": "especially"
    },
    {
        "Question": "noticed",
        "Answer": "observed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "notion",
        "Answer": "idea",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "not reached consensus on",
        "Answer": "not agreed on",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "novel",
        "Answer": "innovative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "no wander",
        "Answer": "unsurprising",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "now and then",
        "Answer": "occasionally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "no wonder",
        "Answer": "unsurprising",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "objection",
        "Answer": "arguments in opposition",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "objective",
        "Answer": "purpose",
        "Options": "unbiased"
    },
    {
        "Question": "obliged",
        "Answer": "required",
        "Options": "responsible"
    },
    {
        "Question": "obscure",
        "Answer": "little known",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "observation",
        "Answer": "finding",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obsession with",
        "Answer": "fixation on",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obsolete",
        "Answer": "out of date",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obstruction",
        "Answer": "barrier",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obtained",
        "Answer": "gathered",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obviously",
        "Answer": "clearly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "occasionally",
        "Answer": "once in a while",
        "Options": "sometimes"
    },
    {
        "Question": "on balance",
        "Answer": " overall",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "optimal",
        "Answer": "ideal",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "optimistic",
        "Answer": "hopeful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "optimize",
        "Answer": "make the best use of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "option",
        "Answer": "choice",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outbreak",
        "Answer": "sudden increase",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outdated",
        "Answer": "old-fashioned",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outlining",
        "Answer": "summarizing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outlying",
        "Answer": "far from the center",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "out of sight",
        "Answer": "hidden",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outstanding",
        "Answer": "excellent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outweighs",
        "Answer": "exceeds",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "overall",
        "Answer": "general",
        "Options": "considered as a whole"
    },
    {
        "Question": "overlie",
        "Answer": "cover",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "oversaw",
        "Answer": "supervised",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "overshadowed",
        "Answer": "distracted from",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "overtaken",
        "Answer": "surpassed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "overtaxed",
        "Answer": "heavily burdened",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "overwhelming",
        "Answer": "powerful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "painstakingly",
        "Answer": "with great effort",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pales",
        "Answer": "loses significance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "paradoxes",
        "Answer": "contradictions",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "paradoxically",
        "Answer": "surprisingly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "particular",
        "Answer": "specific",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "peak",
        "Answer": "high point",
        "Options": "maximum"
    },
    {
        "Question": "penchant",
        "Answer": "inclination",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "perceived",
        "Answer": "seen",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "perfected",
        "Answer": "completed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "periodically",
        "Answer": "regularly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "perishable",
        "Answer": "likely to decay",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "perpetuated",
        "Answer": "continued",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "perplexed",
        "Answer": "puzzled",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "persisted",
        "Answer": "continued",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "persistent",
        "Answer": "lasting",
        "Options": "enduring"
    },
    {
        "Question": "perspective",
        "Answer": "viewpoint",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "persuasively",
        "Answer": "convincingly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pertinent",
        "Answer": "relevant",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pervasive",
        "Answer": "widespread",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pessimistic",
        "Answer": "negative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "phenomenon",
        "Answer": "occurrence",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pierced",
        "Answer": "broke through",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pinpoint",
        "Answer": "identify precisely",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pioneering",
        "Answer": "original/ introduced",
        "Options": "leader"
    },
    {
        "Question": "placed",
        "Answer": "deposited",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "plague",
        "Answer": "cause trouble for",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "plausible",
        "Answer": "believable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "plugged",
        "Answer": "filled up",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "plunge",
        "Answer": "drop",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pointed out",
        "Answer": "stated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pondered",
        "Answer": "thought about",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "portable",
        "Answer": "moveable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "portrayed",
        "Answer": "depicted",
        "Options": "represented"
    },
    {
        "Question": "posed",
        "Answer": "presented",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "posterity",
        "Answer": "future generations",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "postulated",
        "Answer": "hypothesized",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "potent",
        "Answer": "powerful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "potential",
        "Answer": "possible",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "precisely",
        "Answer": "exactly",
        "Options": "accurately"
    },
    {
        "Question": "prediction",
        "Answer": "expectation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "predominate",
        "Answer": "are in the majority",
        "Options": "principal/ mainly"
    },
    {
        "Question": "preoccupation",
        "Answer": "concern",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "preposterous",
        "Answer": "unbelievable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prerequisite",
        "Answer": "requirement",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "preserving",
        "Answer": "maintaining",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prestige",
        "Answer": "status",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prestigious",
        "Answer": "highly regarded",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "presumably",
        "Answer": "it is reasonable to assume",
        "Options": "supposedly"
    },
    {
        "Question": "prevail",
        "Answer": "dominate",
        "Options": "most frequent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "prime",
        "Answer": "high-quality",
        "Options": "superior"
    },
    {
        "Question": "primordial",
        "Answer": "present at the very beginning ",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "principally",
        "Answer": "mainly",
        "Options": "major"
    },
    {
        "Question": "prior to",
        "Answer": "before",
        "Options": "preceding"
    },
    {
        "Question": "pristine",
        "Answer": "pure",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prized",
        "Answer": "valued",
        "Options": ""
    }
]